{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Top Gun",
      "description": "Quotes from the movie Top Gun",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "name": "Deck 11",
      "description": "Descrip Deck 1",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "name": "Big Lewbowski",
      "description": "Let me explain something to you. Um, I am not \"Mr. Lebowski\". You're Mr. Lebowski. I'm the Dude. So that's what you call me. You know, that or, uh, His Dudeness, or uh, Duder, or El Duderino if you're not into the whole brevity thing.",
      "id": 9
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "card 1 ",
      "back": "card 1",
      "deckId": 8,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "card 2",
      "back": "card 2",
      "deckId": 8,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "card 3",
      "back": " card 3",
      "deckId": 8,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "card 5",
      "back": "card 6",
      "deckId": 8,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "Intro",
      "back": "March 3, 1969 the United States Navy established an elite school for the top one percent of its pilots. Its purpose was to teach the lost art of aerial combat and to insure that the handful of men who graduated were the best fighter pilots in the world. They succeeded. Today, the Navy calls it Fighter Weapons School. The flyers call it: TOP GUN.",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "Stinger",
      "back": " For five weeks, you're gonna fly against the best fighter pilots in the world. You were number two, Cougar was number one. Cougar lost it, turned in his wings. You guys are number one. But you remember one thing. You screw up just this much, you'll be flying a cargo plane full of rubber dog shit out of Hong Kong.",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "new card 1",
      "back": "new card 2",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "Adding a card",
      "back": "To get enough cards",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "Adding another card",
      "back": "because there still arent enough",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "Adding a third card",
      "back": "to really be sure ",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "Donnie",
      "back": "I am the walrus.",
      "deckId": 9,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "Walter",
      "back": "Smokey, my friend, you are entering a world of pain.\nThe Dude: Walter...\nWalter Sobchak: You mark that frame an 8, and you're entering a world of pain.\nSmokey: I'm not...\nWalter Sobchak: A world of pain.\nSmokey: Dude, he's your partner...\nWalter Sobchak: [shouting] Has the whole world gone crazy? Am I the only one around here who gives a shit about the rules? Mark it zero!",
      "deckId": 9,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "The Dude ",
      "back": "Let me explain something to you. Um, I am not \"Mr. Lebowski\". You're Mr. Lebowski. I'm the Dude. So that's what you call me. You know, that or, uh, His Dudeness, or uh, Duder, or El Duderino if you're not into the whole brevity thing.",
      "deckId": 9,
      "id": 20
    }
  ]
}